https://www.law-help.com/cookie-policy/

Skip NavigationAbout UsContact UsToggle navigation HomeMeet Our AttorneysHarold DwinMatthew FarrAndrew RodabaughAnn Wittik-BravmannBarry CohenSee All AttorneysPersonal InjuryPersonal Injury OverviewCar AccidentsDog BitesDrug RecallMotorcycle AccidentsNursing Home NeglectProduct LiabilityPedestrian AccidentsTruck AccidentsWorkers’ CompMedical MalpracticeCriminal LawContact Us
Cookie Policy Last updated November 01, 2019This Cookie Policy explains how Cohen and Dwin, P.A. (“Company“, “we“, “us“, and “our“) uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our websites at https://www.law-help.com/, (“Websites“). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.In some cases we may use cookies to collect personal information, or that becomes personal information if we combine it with other information.What are cookies?Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, Cohen and Dwin, P.A.) are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “third party cookies”. Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.Why do we use cookies?We use first and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites to operate, and we refer to these as “essential” or “strictly necessary” cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):How can I control cookies?You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie rights by setting your preferences in the Cookie Consent Manager. The Cookie Consent Manager allows you to select which categories of cookies you accept or reject. Essential cookies cannot be rejected as they are strictly necessary to provide you with services.The Cookie Consent Manager can be found in the notification banner and on our website. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. You may also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information.In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com.The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described in the table below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):Essential website cookies:These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our Websites and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas.Name: __tlbcpvPurpose: Used to record the cookie consent preferences of visitorsProvider: .termly.ioService: Termly View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 20 yearsName: __tltpl_#Purpose: Used to record the policies that visitors consent toProvider: .termly.ioService: Termly View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 20 yearsName: __tluidPurpose: Assigns a random ID number to each visitor so that their policy consent and cookie consent preferences can be saved.Provider: .termly.ioService: Termly View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 20 yearsName: JSESSIONIDPurpose: Used to maintain an anonymous user session by the server in JavaTM 2 Platform Enterprise Edition web applications. It is a necessary cookie that expires at the end of a session.Provider: www.law-help.comService: JavaServer Pages Technologies View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: __cfduidPurpose: Used by Cloudflare to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address, and apply security settings on a per-client basis. This is a HTTP type cookie that expires after 1 year.Provider: .ngagelive.comService: CloudFlare View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 12 months 5 daysName: ASP.NET_SessionIdPurpose: Used by Microsoft .NET-based sites to maintain an anonymized user session by the server. This cookie expires at the end of a browsing session which is determined by the application configuration.Provider: messenger.ngageics.comService: .NET platform View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: __cfduidPurpose: Used by Cloudflare to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address, and apply security settings on a per-client basis. This is a HTTP type cookie that expires after 1 year.Provider: .ngageics.comService: CloudFlare View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 12 months 5 daysPerformance and functionality cookies:These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our Websites but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality (like videos) may become unavailable.Name: GPSPurpose: A session cookie that registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.Expires after 30 minutes.Provider: .youtube.comService: Youtube View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 30 minutesName: BIGipServer#Purpose: Used to monitor page load speed as part of site performance monitoring. It is also a HTTP cookie type that expire as a session ends.Provider: scripting.ngagelive.comService: BIG-IP Product Suite View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionAnalytics and customization cookies:These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Websites for you.Name: _gat#Purpose: Enables Google Analytics regulate the rate of requesting. It is a HTTP cookie type that lasts for a session.Provider: .law-help.comService: Google Analytics View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 1 minuteName: _gidPurpose: Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is a HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session.Provider: .law-help.comService: Google Analytics View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 1 dayName: _gaPurpose: It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is a HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years.Provider: .law-help.comService: Google Analytics View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 1 year 12 months 4 daysAdvertising cookies:These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you. They perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.Name: _fbpPurpose: Facebook tracking pixel used to identify visitors for personalized advertising.Provider: .law-help.comService: Facebook View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 3 monthsName: IDEPurpose: Used to measure the conversion rate of ads presented to the user. Expires in 1.5 years.Provider: .doubleclick.netService: DoubleClick View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 1 year 12 months 4 daysName: ga-audiencesPurpose: Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor’s online behaviour across websitesProvider: www.law-help.comService: AdWords View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: VISITOR_INFO1_LIVEPurpose: YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time.Provider: .youtube.comService: YouTube View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 6 monthsName: tr/Purpose: Facebook tracking pixel used to identify visitors for personalized advertising.Provider: www.law-help.comService: Facebook View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: IrelandType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: frPurpose: Used by Facebook to collect a unique browser and user ID, used for targeted advertising.Provider: .facebook.comService: Facebook View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: IrelandType: http_cookieExpires in: 3 monthsName: test_cookiePurpose: A session cookie used to check if the user’s browser supports cookies.Provider: .doubleclick.netService: DoubleClick View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 15 minutesName: YSCPurpose: YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time.Provider: .youtube.comService: YouTube View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionSocial networking cookies:These cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content that you find interesting on our Websites through third party social networking and other websites. These cookies may also be used for advertising purposes.Name: _pinterest_cmPurpose: Enables Pinterest to keep their service usage in check. This is a HTTP cookie type that expires after 1 year.Provider: .pinterest.comService: Pinterest View Service Privacy PolicyCountry: United StatesType: http_cookieExpires in: 12 months 5 daysUnclassified cookies:These are cookies that have not yet been categorized. We are in the process of classifying these cookies with the help of their providers.Name: BrowserHeightPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 7980 yearsName: CFIDPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: BROWSERWIDTHPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: DOMAINNAMEIDPurpose: __________Provider: .law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 29 years 11 months 27 daysName: LEVELPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: CFTOKENPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: server_cookieExpires in: 1 dayName: PHPMEMBERIDPurpose: __________Provider: .www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 1 dayName: MEMBERIDPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: ngageIdPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 4 years 12 months 4 daysName: CUSTOMERIDPurpose: __________Provider: .law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 29 years 11 months 27 daysName: BrowserWidthPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 7980 yearsName: CUSTOMERIDPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: VIPMEMBERIDPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionName: ngageFirstVisitPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 12 months 5 daysName: CFGLOBALSPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: 29 years 11 months 27 daysName: DOMAINNAMEIDPurpose: __________Provider: www.law-help.comService: __________Country: CanadaType: http_cookieExpires in: sessionWhat about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called “tracking pixels” or “clear gifs”). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites or opened an e-mail including them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within a website to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to the website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of e-mail marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning.Do you use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?Websites may also use so-called “Flash Cookies” (also known as Local Shared Objects or “LSOs”) to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of our services, fraud prevention and for other site operations.If you do not want Flash Cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash Cookies storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash Cookies by going to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash Cookies (referred to “information” on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash Cookies that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time).Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash Cookies may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with our services or online content.Do you serve targeted advertising?Third parties may serve cookies on your computer or mobile device to serve advertising through our Websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. They may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. This can be accomplished by them using cookies or web beacons to collect information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details or other details that directly identify you unless you choose to provide these.How often will you update this Cookie Policy?We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please therefore re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies.The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.Where can I get further information?If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at braddwin@cohendwin.com or by post to:Cohen and Dwin, P.A.9505 Reisterstown Rd Suite 1Owings Mills, MD 21117United StatesPhone: (+1) 410-653-6000
Harold Dwin Co-Founder
Since 1977, our Maryland personal injury lawyers, workers' comp attorneys, and criminal defense lawyers have been helping individuals and families successfully resolve stressful legal matters.
Meet Harold, Attorney at Law
Popular Posts
Peace Orders and Protection Orders, What’s the Difference? Is Baltimore the Heroin Capital of America? Should I Refuse a Field Sobriety Test in Maryland? Maryland Workers Comp: Electric Shock The Five Most Common Workplace Accidents and How to Prevent Them
